Julia Connelly

Software Engineer

Contact

Address

Milwaukee, WI, 53222

Phone

9526881450

E-mail

juliakconnelly@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/jkconnelly

Technical Profile

Proficiencies

- C++
- Python
- Java
- Linux
- Git
- Docker
- Cucumber
- Jenkins
- Spring Framework
- MATLAB
- OpenAPI

Familiarities

- C#
- .NET
- SQL
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- OneAPI
- Amazon Web Services

Software engineer with 5+ years of experience and a B.A. and an M.A. in Computer Science. A quick-learning and curious worker experienced with a wide variety of technologies. Enjoys taking ownership of projects. Often recognized for clean code, innovative use of software patterns, and being a fun team member.

Work History

2018-07 -Current

Software Engineer

GE Healthcare, Waukesha, WI

- Worked on the Magnetic Resonance (MR) Image Reconstruction team.
- Adapted the reconstruction engine code into a consumable C++, Matlab, and Python SDK for internal and research stakeholders.
- Developed new clinical features in a complex, modern system with multiple communication pathways, micro-services, and custom firmware and hardware.
- Wrote and implemented test cases across sub-systems at the unit, component, and integration test levels.

2017-06 -2017-08

Software Engineering Intern

Applied Predictive Technologies, Arrington, VA

- Contributed product code within 1 month of joining the team.
- Collaborated with other engineers, QA, and the product team to implement and test a brand new line chart feature.

Education

2019-08 -2021-12 Master of Science: Computer Science

Johns Hopkins University - Baltimore, MD

2014-09 -2018-06 **Bachelor of Arts: Computer Science**

Carleton College - Northfield, MN

Coursework

C, React Native, Firebase, Arduino, OpenCL, Cuda, Hadoop, Hive, Apache Pig, Spark, Apache Tomcat